Guide to the Aubrey Wisberg Papers c.1945-1970 MSS 48 MSS.048
Fales Library and Special Collections
Aubrey Wisberg Papers
c.1945-1970
Fales Library and Special Collections
Wisberg, Aubrey
MSS.048
16.5 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
Aubrey Wisberg, film and television writer and producer died in New York City in 1990 at the age of 78. His papers consist of typescripts for his film and television productions, and draft copies of his novels, short stories and plays. The collection also includes a small portion of correspondence, photos, and promotional materials relating to specific film or television productions.
Provenance
The Aubrey Wisberg Papers were donated to the Fales Library by Maura Jacobsen in September of 1994.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Aubrey Lionel Wisberg was born in London, England. He immigrated to the United States in 1921, attended New York University and Columbia University, and married Barbara Duberstein. Wisberg made his career as a screenwriter, director, and producer with credits in more than 40 films including The Big Fix and The Man from Planet X. Three of his early screenplays were World War II movies: Counter-Espionage and Submarine Raider in 1942 and They Came to Blow Up America in 1943. Mr. Wisberg's 1945 film The Horn Blows at Midnight starred the comedian Jack Benny.
Wisberg was associate producer for Edward Small Productions; founder and executive producer for Wisberg Productions; and co-founder of American Pictures Corporation and Mid-Century Films. Production credits for Mid-Century Film include, The Man From Planet X (1951), Return to Treasure Island (1954) and Murder Is My Beat (1955).
Wisberg was the author of several books, including Patrol Boat 999, Savage Soldiers, This Is the Life and Bushman at Large. Wisberg was also a radio and television dramatist in the United States, Australia, and England; a radio diffusionist in Paris; and a journalist. He won the International Unity Award, from the Inter-Racial Society, for The Burning Cross.
Aubrey Wisberg died of cancer in 1990 in New York City. He was 78 years old.
Scope and Content Note
The Aubrey Wisberg Papers consist of typescripts for his film and television productions, and draft copies of his novels, short stories and plays. The collection also includes a small portion of correspondence, photos, and promotional materials relating to specific film or television productions.
Arrangement
Materials are arranged alphabetically by production title. Duplicate copies of scripts are grouped in the same folder, and copies with annotations or anomalies have been foldered separately.
Missing Title
Series I: Film and Television Production Typescripts
Series II: Miscellaneous Materials
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
Hammond Film Script Collection (MSS.076)
Separated Material
Monographs have been separated and catalogued individually. These items can be searched in Bobcat through the name of the work, author or provenance information.
Motion picture plays.; Motion picture plays.; Photographs.; Photographs.; Correspondence.; Correspondence.; Typescripts; Typescripts; Scrapbooks.; Scrapbooks.; B films.; B films.; Feature films.; Feature films.; Science fiction films.; Science fiction films.; Horror films.; Horror films.; Motion picture producers and directors.; Motion picture producers and directors.; Audiocassettes.; Audiocassettes.; Television plays.; Television plays.; Awards; Awards; Posters.; Posters.; Audiotapes.; Audiotapes.; Wisberg, Aubrey; Schwarzenegger, Arnold; Schwarzenegger, Arnold; Pollexfen, Jack, 1908-2003; Pollexfen, Jack, 1908-2003; Wisberg Productions; Wisberg Productions; Warner Bros. Pictures (1923-1967); Warner Bros. Pictures (1923-1967); Gering, Marion, 1901-1977; Gering, Marion, 1901-1977; Edward Small Productions, Inc; Edward Small Productions, Inc; Paramount Pictures Corporation; Paramount Pictures Corporation; Mid-Century Films; Mid-Century Films; American Pictures Corporation; American Pictures Corporation
- Series I: Film and television production typescripts
  Scope and Contents note
  Series 1 contains 9 boxes of Wisberg's typescripts for his film and television productions. There is also one regular-sized box and one oversize flat box of miscellaneous materials, such as correspondence, photographs, promotional/press information, and fragments of typescripts. The collection is processed at the folder level.
  - According to Reliable Sources, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ach, Du Liebe Ada Schmidt! by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Adventures of Don Juan, number one, "The Return" Television Series created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Adventures of Ponce De Leon, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg "The Slave Raiders" written over the title, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Africa, by Aubrey Wisberg, based on a play by Alfred Savior and Leopold Marchand, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - An Afternoon in the Dull Life of Mrs. Mendelbaum, a play in one act by Aubrey Wisberg. Indicates premiere production: the Dubuque (Iowa) society of Fine Arts, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Amazon Patrol, television series, number one "The Fugitive" an original teleplay created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Amateur Sinner, a musical play by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Amateur Sinner, a musical play. Book by Aubrey Wisberg. Lyrics by Victor Matthews. Music by Irwin Webb. Musical score not included, with notes, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arctic Escape, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arctic Escape, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Alternate title: Fugitives from a Million Miles, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Backtrack, television series, episode one "The Secret Gun" created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Blade of Don Juan, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Blemished Bride, by Aubrey Wisberg, marked "Old" on the cover, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Blemished Bride, by Aubrey Wisberg, annotated, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Breed of the Sea Beast, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - By the Beautiful Sea, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Caliph of Paris, by Aubrey Wisberg and Martin Field, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Campus Cop, television series created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Cannibal Queen, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Captain Flint's Fortune, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Casanova's Last Night, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Indicates "Purchased by Paramount Pictures Corp. for the Technicolor film Casanova's Big Night starring Bob Hope and Joan Fontaine" [Produced 1954], undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Casanova's Last Night, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Indicates "Sold to Paramount Pictures" in handwriting, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Castle of the Damned, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610019 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Casualty, by Aubrey Wisberg and Jack Pollexfen. Indicates "Sold to Warner Bros. Pictures. Produced in the 'Sunset Strip' television series.", undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cause for Alarm, by Aubrey Wisberg. Indicates, "First serial rights offered only", undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - City Cinderellas, an original story by Aubrey Wisberg, first treatment, October 11, 1941, 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Closed Book, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Comeback, dramatic series by Aubrey Wisberg. First draft screenplay December 10, 1952. Sent to Richard Sanville, 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Compound One, written and created by Aubrey Wisberg. Number one "The Godbeast" an original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Congo, number one "The Fugitive" created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Congo, half hour television series by Aubrey Wisberg, number one "The Godbeast" original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Congo, half hour television series by Aubrey Wisberg, number one "The Godbeast" original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, with addenda, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Congo, number two, "The Fugitive" original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Congo, number two, "The Silent Alarm" created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Congo, number four, "The Invisible Terror" created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Congo, number four, "The Invisible Terror" created and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Congo, number five, "The Hostages" original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Congo, number six, "The Endless Night" original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Congo, number seven, "The Silent Alarm" original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Congo, number eight, "The Rain Forest" conceived and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Congo, number eight, "The Rain Forest" conceived and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Congorama, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Crime of Violence, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Crime of Violence, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Mitchell Gertz label inside cover, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Crime of Violence, a play in three acts by Aubrey Wisberg, manuscript, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Crime of Violence, a play in three acts by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Devil in the Wind, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Devil in the Wind, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Includes clipping "Calls 'New Water' Threat to Earth" October 10, Post, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Devil in the Wind, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dreamboat, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Duel on the Moon, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Duel on the Moon, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Newspaper clipping "Contract let for Rocket to Propel a Spaceman", undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Duel on the Moon, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Bound by Studio Duplicating Service, Inc., undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Duel on the Planet Mars, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Produced under the title Mission: Mars by Allied Artists Pictures and American Broadcasting Company, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Eighth Day of the Week, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Eighth Day of the Week, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610027 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Eighth Day of the Week, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Includes shot lists, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Eighth Day of the Week, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. "Jose Ferrar wanted to direct it" written on title page, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - An Evening at Home, a play in three acts by Audrey Wisberg. Four copies, slightly differing title pages, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - An Evening at Home, a play in three acts by Audrey Wisberg. Additional pages included, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - An Evening at Home, a play in three acts by Audrey Wisberg. Synopsis included, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Evil in the Blood, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 119 page version, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Evil in the Blood, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 123 page version, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - First Voyage, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fish Out of Water, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Flesh and the Flower, original story by Aubrey Wisberg and Marion Gering, screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Flesh and the Flower, original story by Aubrey Wisberg and Marion Gering, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Flesh and the Flower, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - For Love or Money, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Fortunes of David Copperfield, designed and written by Aubrey Wisberg. Pitch for television show and cover page to episode one. Number two script, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The Fortunes of David Copperfield, number one, designed and written by Aubrey Wisberg. Five copies, slightly differing covers, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - The Fortunes of David Copperfield, number two, designed and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Fortunes of Don Juan, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg and Jack Pollexfen, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fortunes of Don Juan, by Aubrey Wisberg and Jack Pollexfen. Numbered "number one", undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fugitives From a Million Miles, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Gentlemen Friend, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Get Off My Back... You Bitch, a play in three acts by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - God Is Alive and Well and Living Ev'reywhere! Book by Aubrey Wisberg, music and lyrics by Gene Bone and Howard Fenton, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - God is Alive and Well and Living Ev'reywhere, concept, lyrics and music by Gene Bone and Howard Fenton. Variety Magazine article included "Disk Biz Sees the Light in Gospel Music" May 25, 1977, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Good Samaritan, a play in one act and eight episodes by Aubrey Wisberg (with a bow to Charles Dickens), undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Heartbreak, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hell Without Heat, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 139(140) page numeration, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hell Without Heat, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 118(121) page numeration, undated; 0031142040610035 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Hell Without Heat, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 117(120) page numeration, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hello Girl, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg and Jack Pollexfen, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hello Girl, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg and Jack Pollexfen. "Ilse Lahn" written on cover, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding Hercules October 8, 1954 - July 9, 1959, 1954-1959; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hercules Unchained, Lux-Galatea Production Poster, Daily Variety, April 19, 1960, 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hercules, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hercules and the Queen of Evil, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hercules in New York, promotional materials, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hercules in New York Poster. See map case, undated; 0031142040610043 (Folder 9)
  - Hercules in New York, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Copies of correspondence from Arnold Schwarzenegger to Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Hickory Stick, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Horn of Plenty, original story by Aubrey Wisberg, screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg and Jack Pollexfen, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - House on Fire, teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Hunter "Shadow at Noon," original teleplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - I Love You Again, by Aubrey Wisberg and Charles Smith, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - I Was a Teen Age Mutineer, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Island Adventure, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - It Just Isn't Done! by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - It's a Woman's World, television series created by Aubrey Wisberg, episode one: "An Afternoon in the Dull Life of Mrs. Mendelbaum", undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - It's Only Money, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 118 pages, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - It's Only Money, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 117 pages., undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Judas Doll, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - King of the Gypsies, by Aubrey Wisberg Number one., undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - King of the Gypsies, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Look Who's Talking! Television play by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Love at Sea, by Aubrey Wisberg and Martin Field, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Love That Girl, by Aubrey Wisberg, with notes, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Love That Girl! A lay in one act by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Low Down Woman, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Railroad station opening, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Low Down Woman, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Coffee Shop opening, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Lullaby for Drums, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610043 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Lullaby for Drums, by Aubrey Wisberg, missing pages, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mark of the Gaucho, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mark of the Quarter Moon, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mark of the Yogi, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Midnight Sailing, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 154 page version, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Midnight Sailing, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 155 page version, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Midnight Sailing, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 142 page version, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Midnight Sailing, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, 148 page version., undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Midnight Sailing, synopsis of screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mr. Moscovitz, television series conceived and written by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - More Than Meets the Eye, book by Aubrey Wisberg, lyrics and music by Burt Milton, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Murder Most Fair, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The Narrow Street, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - New Girl in Town, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - New Girl in Town, by Aubrey Wisberg, annotated cover, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Nightshade, a new play by Aubrey Wisberg and Robert Sneddon, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - No Time Like the Present, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - No Time Like the Present, by Aubrey Wisberg Indicates alternate title: Yesterday in Savannah, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - No Time Like the Present, by Aubrey Wisberg, with Reader's Report, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - No Time Like the Present, by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610050 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - One Way Out, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - One Woman's Story, original screenplay by Martin Field and Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Outlaws of Painted Canyon, screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Final Draft, November 20, 1957, Columbia Pictures, 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Outlaws of Painted Canyon, screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg. Revised final draft, April 9, 1958, Columbia Pictures, 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Panic at 1075, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Panic at 1075, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - A Park is for Lovers, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, ending page 123(132), undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - A Park is for Lovers, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg ending page 143(152), undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Passion of Roger Corsair, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Passionate People, book by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Passionate People, original screenplay by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - The Passionate People (a new musical play), libretto by Aubrey Wisberg, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Patrol Boat 999, television series created and written by Aubrey Wisberg. Book information, reviews, and character lists, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Patrol Boat 999, (synopsis of story lines), undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Patrol Boat 999, Aubrey Wisberg. Book information, review excerpts, television series synopsis of plot and format, and author credits., undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Patrol Boat 999: a half-hour weekly TV series, program information, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Patrol Boat 999, by Harold Waters and Aubrey Wisberg. Review Excerpts and photocopy of page 20, undated; 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Patrol Boat 999, "Night Run From Nassau" (pilot script) written by Aubrey Wisberg, second draft, 10/27/1960, 0031142040610068 (Box 6, Folder 18)